Guide to the Fred Ross papers M0812
Department of Special Collections and University Archives
- Series F. Audio & Transcripts (444 tapes)
  - Subseries: Audiocassettes
    - Audiocassettes, numbered 1-72 by Ross
      - 8/9/84. Lorena, Cathy, Jenefer [?], Dan, Jane (Box 36 (OS), Folder 60)
      - 8/9, 8/10 (Box 36 (OS), Folder 61)
      - 8/9-8/10. John, Kent, Jennifer. Jane (Box 36 (OS), Folder 62)
      - 8/10/84 (Box 36 (OS), Folder 63)
      - 8/10/84. Jennifer, Jan. 8/10-8/11. John, Jennifer (Box 36 (OS), Folder 64)
      - untitled (Box 36 (OS), Folder 65)
      - Jennifer, Kent. Discussion and John (Box 36 (OS), Folder 66)
      - 8/11/84 (Box 36 (OS), Folder 67)
      - PM 8/12 (Box 36 (OS), Folder 68)
      - 8/12 (Box 36 (OS), Folder 69)
      - PM 8/12 (Box 36 (OS), Folder 70)
      - PM Sunday 8/12 (Box 36 (OS), Folder 71)
      - PM 8/12/ 8/14 Vibes (Box 36 (OS), Folder 72)
    - Audiocassettes, numbered 73-101 by Ross (missing #98)
      - 8/14 Vibes (Box 37 (OS), Folder 73)
      - 8/14. Kent PM (Box 37 (OS), Folder 74)
      - 8/14 (Box 37 (OS), Folder 75)
      - 8/14 (Box 37 (OS), Folder 76)
      - 8/14/84, begin 8/15 (Box 37 (OS), Folder 77)
      - 8/15/84 (Box 37 (OS), Folder 78)
      - 8/15/84 (Box 37 (OS), Folder 79)
      - 8/15/84 (Box 37 (OS), Folder 80)
      - 8/15/84, begin 8/16 (Box 37 (OS), Folder 81)
      - 8/15/84. Begin 8/16/84 John and Ned. Julie and John (Box 37 (OS), Folder 82)
      - 8/16/84 (Box 37 (OS), Folder 83)
      - 8/16/84. Julie and Jane. Jane, Jennifer, Kent (Box 37 (OS), Folder 84)
      - 8/16/84, begin 8/17 (Box 37 (OS), Folder 85)
      - 8/16/84. 8/17 begin. Kent and Ross. Kent, Jane, Jennifer (Box 37 (OS), Folder 86)
      - 8/17/84 (Box 37 (OS), Folder 87)
      - 8/17/84. Jennifer and John. (Box 37 (OS), Folder 88)
      - 8/17/84 (Box 37 (OS), Folder 89)
      - 8/19. Jennifer, Jane, John (Box 37 (OS), Folder 90)
      - 8/19 (Box 37 (OS), Folder 91)
      - 8/19 (Box 37 (OS), Folder 92)
      - 8/19/84 (Box 37 (OS), Folder 93)
      - Ellie - Fred. 8/21/84 (Box 37 (OS), Folder 94)
      - Paul - Fred. 8/21/84, 8/22/84 (Box 37 (OS), Folder 95)
      - Paul - Fred. 8/22/84, 8/24/84 (Box 37 (OS), Folder 96)
      - Paul - Fred. 8/24/84 (Box 37 (OS), Folder 97)
      - Ellie - Fred. 8/22/84 (Box 37 (OS), Folder 98)
      - Fred. 8/30/84 (Box 37 (OS), Folder 99)
      - 8/30/84 (Box 37 (OS), Folder 100)
      - Fred - Paul - Ellie wrap-up 8/30/84 (Box 37 (OS), Folder 101)
    - Wyler-Cohen interviews, August-September 1985 [originally numbered 1-20, missing cassette originally numbered 13]
      - 8/23/85. First meeting w/ Fred Ross at Neidorf's. Ellie, Barbara, Pam, David, Fred Ross, Sr., Fred Ross, Jr., Anna Marie N. (Box 37 (OS), Folder 102)
      - 8/23/85. Ellie and Barbara (Box 37 (OS), Folder 103)
      - 8/24. Band on stage. Testimonial. (Box 37 (OS), Folder 104)
      - Band, Cesar, Tony Rios, Roybal, Luis, Fred Ross, Sr., Fred Ross, Jr. (Box 37 (OS), Folder 105)
      - 8-24-85. Fred (Box 37 (OS), Folder 106)
      - 8/25. Fred Ross, Jr., John Brown (Box 37 (OS), Folder 107)
      - 8/25/85. John Brown. 8/26/85. Fred Ross, Tony Rios (Box 37 (OS), Folder 108)
      - 8/26/85. Fred Ross (Box 37 (OS), Folder 109)
      - 8/26/85 and 8/27/85. Fred Ross (Box 37 (OS), Folder 110)
      - 8/27/85 (Box 37 (OS), Folder 111)
      - 8/28/85. F.R. tales on organizing House Mtg. (Box 37 (OS), Folder 112)
      - 8/28/85. Fred at Motel 6 (Box 37 (OS), Folder 113)
      - 8/28/85. Delano - DiGiorgio. Driving North on Hwy 99 (Box 37 (OS), Folder 114)
      - 8/28/85. Fred b/f Modesto. (Box 37 (OS), Folder 115)
      - 8/29/85. Kay. Fred (Box 37 (OS), Folder 116)
      - 8/29/85. Fred. Interview - Marin County (Box 37 (OS), Folder 117)
      - 8/29/85. Fred Interview in Marin City (Box 37 (OS), Folder 118)
      - untitled (Box 37 (OS), Folder 119)
      - Test tape (Box 37 (OS), Folder 120)
    - Audiocassettes, 1972-75
      - Nov. 9, 1972. With God ain't it a caution. Phoning - Personal visit pitch. Jo M. Tobin. Fred Ross. Prep. for Hs. Mtg. - Reminding. Phoning (Box 38 (OS), Folder 121)
      - 10/73. Beginning of History to Giumarra. Ross Hs Mtg Matilda's (Box 38 (OS), Folder 122)
      - LA, 4/74. Fred Ross. Hist. of Cesar UFW up to loss of contract in 1973 (Box 38 (OS), Folder 123)
      - April 2, 1974. Fred Ross. House Meeting. Origin of house meeting. Personal visist. LA Boycott in 1966-67 (Box 38 (OS), Folder 124)
      - LA, April 2, 1974. The H.M. Church off USC campus (Box 38 (OS), Folder 125)
      - NY, 5/23/74. More sample phone calls. Ross Tr. session. (Box 38 (OS), Folder 126)
      - [NY, 5/23/74?]. Reports from role playing, 1-1 meeting. Fred Ross, 1974 (Box 38 (OS), Folder 127)
      - LA, 7/3/74 (Box 38 (OS), Folder 128)
      - LA 7/4/74 (Box 38 (OS), Folder 129)
      - New York, 9/25/74. Phone calls (Box 38 (OS), Folder 130)
      - 9/27/74. Fred Ross. Area-wide mtg., Dolores at the end. Chris Hartmire (Box 38 (OS), Folder 131)
      - 10/9/74 Los Angeles. Ross. Intro to H. Mtg. Origin of it. Discussion of phoning and winning [?] 1st contact (Box 38 (OS), Folder 132)
      - Dayton, 10/28/74. Fred Ross session. St. Leonard's Seminary. Human nature. My own background. SRA-FAS-WPA-ACRR. Early org. disasters in S.B.-B.T. Mass mtgs. - org of orgs/ - one-to-one. Advantages of Hs Mtg. Spread truth not claims. Peer pressure. Overcoming alibis for not holding Hs. Mtgs. (Box 38 (OS), Folder 133)
      - Dayton, 10/28/74. F.R. session. Human behavior. Finding 1st person. Peer pressure, overcoming alibis. Phone call. (Box 38 (OS), Folder 134)
      - [Dayton, October 1974?] Preparing for simulated phone call. Phone phobia (Box 38 (OS), Folder 135)
      - [Dayton, October 1974?] More on phoning. Hs. Mtg. How to hit - animo. High points to hit at P. visit. Nancy and Joe Toshi [?]story (Box 38 (OS), Folder 136)
      - [Dayton, October 1974?]. Transcribed. Explanation of P.V. Ross. David Martinez et al.- Columbus (Box 38 (OS), Folder 137)
      - [Dayton, October 1974?]. Critique of Martinez PV. PV organizers from Columubus and critique. McGowan's P.V. Luisa [illeg.] the tractor story. Jenny Brashear's sacrifice (Box 38 (OS), Folder 138)
      - [Dayton, October 1974?]. P.V. Eliseo's report on sim'd P.V. Eliseo's explanation of NLRA question. H Mtg. (Box 38 (OS), Folder 139)
      - [Dayton, October 1974?] Reports from PV sim'd mtgs. Prep for Hs Mtgs. Waves of Immigrants. Arabs. Beginning of hs Mtg. Outline (Box 38 (OS), Folder 140)
      - Dayton [October 1974?]. From = power situation [illeg.] to Cesar following outline of Hs Meeting. Bloody Xmas. I meet Cesar to org. of NFWA (Box 38 (OS), Folder 141)
      - [Dayton, October 1974?] '65 Strike to Penelli-Minetti. Gallo to Lettuce Boycott. Hs Mtg Outline (Box 38 (OS), Folder 142)
      - [Dayton, October 1974?] Victory in Grapes, affect [sic] on wkrs. Org. of Delano [illeg.] 1971. Dolores Mendoza. Florida, Bloody Summer '73 (Box 38 (OS), Folder 143)
      - [Dayton, October 1974?]. Hs Mtg conclusion. Chris, Sam [illeg.] (Box 38 (OS), Folder 144)
      - 11/2/74 [Dayton?]. Hs. Mtgs. Baca Hernandez, [illeg.] reports on sim Hs Mtgs. (Box 38 (OS), Folder 145)
      - 11/2/74 [Dayton?]. Forms, record keeping, [illeg.] your day. Daily Mtgs. Support groups. Monitoring phoning, PV, H Mtgs, Parrish pattern of org. (Box 38 (OS), Folder 146)
      - 11/2/74 [Dayton?]. Area-wide Mtg. (Box 38 (OS), Folder 147)
      - 11/2/74 [Dayton?]. Area-wide org. (Box 38 (OS), Folder 148)
      - 11/2/74 [Dayton?]. AW Mtg and after. Chirs Hartmire (Box 38 (OS), Folder 149)
      - 11/2/74 [Dayton?]. Chirs Hartmire. CH and FR, Discipline (Box 38 (OS), Folder 150)
      - 11/2/74 [Dayton?]. Discipline (Box 38 (OS), Folder 151)
      - 11/2/74 [Dayton?]. End of session (Box 38 (OS), Folder 152)
      - NY, 1974. Fred Ross. P.V.'s, phoning. UFW (Box 38 (OS), Folder 153)
      - 1/75. Discussion on Hs Mtg. Steffan. Dolores and Frank Ortiz (Box 38 (OS), Folder 154)
      - NY, Jan. 1975. Washington Square Mtg. (Box 38 (OS), Folder 155)
      - 1/6/75. Training Session. History of HM (Box 38 (OS), Folder 156)
      - 1/7/75. Phoning Critique. Personal Visit (Box 38 (OS), Folder 157)
      - 1/7/75. Personal Visit. Role playing (Box 38 (OS), Folder 158)
      - 1/7/75. Training session. Outline of House Mtg. Phoning (Box 38 (OS), Folder 159)
      - 3/10/75. Training session. Boycott. CC and the strike, Florida. Hist of Farm Labor (Box 38 (OS), Folder 160)
      - 3/10/75. Training session. History - Gallo strike. 1967 - Guimarra - Boycott - Victory - Lettuce strike 1970 - Fast - Salinas Violence - effect on wkrs of contract (Box 38 (OS), Folder 161)
      - 3/10/75. Training session. Mark Lyons (Box 38 (OS), Folder 162)
      - 3/10/75. Training Session. Black Problem - Florida organizing (Box 38 (OS), Folder 163)
      - 3/11/75, Florida. Training session. The first contact. Sim'd phone calls (Box 38 (OS), Folder 164)
      - 3/11/75, Florida. Sim'd PV's. Dianna - Mark (Box 38 (OS), Folder 165)
      - 3/11/75, Florida. PV critique. HM. Ross. Nancy. Slavery story (Box 38 (OS), Folder 166)
      - 3/11/75, 3/12/75, Florida. Training session. Salinas strike. Practice Hm's (Box 38 (OS), Folder 167)
      - 3/11/75, Florida. Ross, sim'd PV (Box 38 (OS), Folder 168)
      - 3/11/75, Florida. Job of coordinator. How I met Dolores (Box 38 (OS), Folder 169)
      - 3/12/75. Ross, prep for A.W.O. Blame others (Box 38 (OS), Folder 170)
      - 3/11/75. DiGiorgio (Box 38 (OS), Folder 171)
      - 3/13/75. AW Org. (Box 38 (OS), Folder 172)
      - 3/13/75. Discipline - Disrupters (Box 38 (OS), Folder 173)
      - 3/13/75. Training session. Recruiting nuns and students (Box 38 (OS), Folder 174)
      - 3/13/75. AW Org. (Box 38 (OS), Folder 175)
      - April 1975, La Paz. Phoning. Poor people's union (Box 38 (OS), Folder 176)
      - 7/1/75. Training session. Control growers (Box 38 (OS), Folder 177)
      - 7/22/75. La Paz Elect. org. (Box 38 (OS), Folder 178)
      - 7/22/75. La Paz Elect. Org. Session (Box 38 (OS), Folder 179)
      - 7/22/75. La Paz (Box 38 (OS), Folder 180)
      - 7/22/75. La Paz Elect. Org. (Box 38 (OS), Folder 181)
      - 7/23/75. La Paz Elect. Org. (Box 38 (OS), Folder 182)
      - 7/23/75. La Paz Elect. Org. (Box 38 (OS), Folder 183)
      - 7/24/75. La Paz Election Organizer Training Session (Box 38 (OS), Folder 184)
      - 7/28/75. La Paz Election Organizer Training Session (Box 38 (OS), Folder 185)
      - 7/28/75. La Paz Election Organizer Training Session. The Personal Visit (Box 38 (OS), Folder 186)
      - 7/28/75, 7/29/85. La Paz Election Organizer Training Session (Box 38 (OS), Folder 187)
      - 7/29/75. La Paz Election Organizer Training Session (Box 38 (OS), Folder 188)
      - 7/29/75. La Paz Election Organizer Training Session (Box 38 (OS), Folder 189)
      - 7/30/75. La Paz Election Organizer Training Session. House meetings (Box 38 (OS), Folder 190)
      - 7/30/75. La Paz Election Organizer Training Session. House meetings (Box 38 (OS), Folder 191)
      - Oct. 1975. Delano (Box 38 (OS), Folder 192)
      - 1975. Stories Santa Ana 1986, LA 1934. Cesat with F. Wks H.M. Boston session (Box 38 (OS), Folder 193)
      - 1975, La Paz. Training session. Marshall's group. Elections (Box 38 (OS), Folder 194)
      - 1975, La Paz. Elections. Marshal's [sic] crew. Phone call (Box 38 (OS), Folder 195)
      - 1975, La Paz. Training. Marshal's [sic] group (Box 38 (OS), Folder 196)
    - Audiocassettes, 1976-78
      - 12/6/76. Oakland Tr. Sess. Boycott Prog. for 1977. Discussion on recruiting (Box 39 (OS), Folder 197)
      - 12/6/76. Oakland training. Screening applicants. AWO discussion. The "Crunch." Money. Action Programs. Sadie Story. J.B. Story - I can't leave until I get 2 HM's. Blazing eyes. (Box 39 (OS), Folder 198)
      - Dec. 1976. Alameda Boycott training. Phoning (Ross). San Francisco and Los Angeles. Streisand story. (Box 39 (OS), Folder 199)
      - 12/1976. Oakland Training Session. Value of College. P.V.'s. Recruitment. Nancy Elliot and "guilty-here" story. (Box 39 (OS), Folder 200)
      - 12/1976. Oakland Tr. Sess. PM. P.V.'s. N. Elliot's cancellation [?] story. (Box 39 (OS), Folder 201)
      - 12/6/76, Oakland. Mini training session on recruiting. Background, 1965-1976 (Box 39 (OS), Folder 202)
      - [1976?]. Historia del movimiento campero en Santa Maria, 1968-1976. Canciones de la huelga. Poemas (Box 39 (OS), Folder 203)
      - 1/5/77. 1st L.A. Session. The way it was to the Orange Strike in 1936. LA Boycott Training 1/5/77. Power of Growers to unify Braceros (Oxnard story with Cesar) (Box 39 (OS), Folder 204)
      - Jan. 1977. LA Boycott Training 3. Di Giorgio story. March to Sacramento (Box 39 (OS), Folder 205)
      - 1/77, LA. Soft sell approach. Boycott training (Box 39 (OS), Folder 206)
      - [Jan. 1977?, LA?] L.A. Training. Discipline. Nick Jones stuff (Box 39 (OS), Folder 207)
      - 1/31/77, Alameda County. Core group session. Lois. (Box 39 (OS), Folder 208)
      - 2/2/77, San Jose. Post Mortem on Core Grp Mtg. [Illeg.] Welch. Dan Bacar. (Box 39 (OS), Folder 209)
      - 2/16 [1977?], New York. 1st training session. Overview. Brooklyn. Mona and Gary. Anna and LA office 1974 (Box 39 (OS), Folder 210)
      - 2/16/77. NY Training Session. Luke gives P.V. (Box 39 (OS), Folder 211)
      - 2/16/77. NY Training Session. Begin review of H. Mtg. Outline. Ross gives P.V. (Box 39 (OS), Folder 212)
      - 2/16/77. NY Training Session. Pt. I of HM Outline. Story of Amelia Diaz firing - PV with me r CC - Action and reaction. Blain McGowan - PV with parents HM in front of Fazzios (Box 39 (OS), Folder 213)
      - 2/16/77. NY Training Session. Macho Story. Period bet. PV and HM2 (Box 39 (OS), Folder 214)
      - 2/18 [1977?]. Brookly Training - Part II - H. Mtg Outline. [Salinas]. Luke gives stories of CC part of outline (Box 39 (OS), Folder 215)
      - 2/18/77. NY Training Session. Pt II Outline. Joe Dukes (Box 39 (OS), Folder 216)
      - 2/18 [1977?]. Brooklyn. Best people on Pt. II of HM Outline. (Box 39 (OS), Folder 217)
      - 2/19/77. NY Training Session. Arizona 1972 - Dave. Part III of HM (Box 39 (OS), Folder 218)
      - 2/19/77. NY Training Session. Part III and IV of HM. Ross give Pt 3 and 4 - good. Salinas, CMLI (Box 39 (OS), Folder 219)
      - 2/20 [1977?], New York. Crunch. Gallo snapshot. Zaninovitch [?] (Box 39 (OS), Folder 220)
      - [Feb. 1977 ?, New York?]. Core group role play, Kim and Claire. Carrol (Box 39 (OS), Folder 221)
      - [Feb. 1977 ?, New York?]. H. Mtg. Roll [sic] play, Mike, Barb, Debbie. Carrol, Sue, Claire, Grady, Luc.- No statistics, stories! (Box 39 (OS), Folder 222)
      - 2/19/77. NY Training Session. Salinas Strike. Jenny Brashears [?] (Box 39 (OS), Folder 223)
      - 4/18/77. Chicago Session (Box 39 (OS), Folder 224)
      - 4/18/77. Chicago Session (Box 39 (OS), Folder 225)
      - 5/30/77. Fred Ross, radio show (Box 39 (OS), Folder 226)
      - 6/12/77. PV's for NSO's Boston training - Ross. Luke arrives (Box 39 (OS), Folder 227)
      - 5/31/77. CORE role play. Greg Costello [?] (Box 39 (OS), Folder 228)
      - 1977. Boston Training Session. Role Playing H.M. Jim (Box 39 (OS), Folder 229)
      - 1977. Boston Training Session. End of Sadie story (Box 39 (OS), Folder 230)
      - [1977?]. Cesar on teaching wkrs to learn and help other wkrs. Wkms. ccamp. (Box 39 (OS), Folder 231)
      - 1/17/78, La Paz (Box 39 (OS), Folder 232)
      - 1/17/78, La Paz (Box 39 (OS), Folder 233)
      - 1/17/78, La Paz (Box 39 (OS), Folder 234)
      - 1/17/78, La Paz (Box 39 (OS), Folder 235)
      - 2/20/78, Oakland. Training session. History. Gary - sim HM (Box 39 (OS), Folder 236)
      - 2/20/78, Oakland. Training session. Map of community - finding the 1st contact - to my [illeg.] org.: history Redlands (Box 39 (OS), Folder 237)
      - 2/20/78. Training session. Vitality - Mary McCarthy, Mona Chacon [?], Gary Clemms [?] - Vitality - animo - phoning. P.V. (Box 39 (OS), Folder 238)
      - 2/20/78, Berkeley. Losers - what if - Jim (Boston) - Pete - LA - Outline for H.M. Training session. "Rapport" - Joe Deety, Mita, Bob Parcel/ HM's (Box 39 (OS), Folder 239)
      - Feb. 20, 1978, Alameda. Training session. History - starting with Gallo "Jews" [?] story (Box 39 (OS), Folder 240)
      - Feb. 20, 1978. Training session. [Illeg.] Brooks - tips on HM's. G. Guthner [?] gives HM with stories. Pt 1 of outline (Box 39 (OS), Folder 241)
      - 2/20/78. Oakland. Training session. Very good. After PV - Phoning - Visits - Mary MC's vitists (Box 39 (OS), Folder 242)
      - 2/21/78, Oakland. Sim H/M. Dan B. (Box 39 (OS), Folder 243)
      - 2/22/78. Oakland Training Session. Mary Mc - NSO. Gary sim'd HM. Jane - sim'd HM (Box 39 (OS), Folder 244)
      - [Feb. 1978?, Oakland?]. Gallo elections, 1975 - seventy guards and cameras - Dan Bacar. Training session. HM III - Ross - history starting with Cesar's birth in Yuma (Box 39 (OS), Folder 245)
      - 2/22/78, Alameda. Lois sim'd H.M. Phoning - Ross. Lois crunches I correct. Mark and Ross - "Nothing to lose" - Chambers advice - [illeg.] talk to men and women together (Box 39 (OS), Folder 246)
      - [Feb. 1978?, Oakland?]. Training session. Lois - HM simulated. Jane - sim'd HM (Box 39 (OS), Folder 247)
      - H.M. Gary starting with CC in Delano movie. C. Chavez HM at Dave Burciagas as told by Ross (Box 39 (OS), Folder 248)
      - 2/21/78 [Oakland?]. CC begins org. of union as told by Jane. HM - Jane - signing of contracts July 1970 (Box 39 (OS), Folder 249)
      - [Feb. 1978? Oakland?]. HM Part III (Box 39 (OS), Folder 250)
      - 2/22/78 [Oakland?]. Training session. Part IV, Crunch. Ross crunches Lois, Mary, Mark, etc. Story on Maggio carrots (Box 39 (OS), Folder 251)
      - 2/22/78. Oakland Training Session. CC at Dave B's house with FWkrs (Box 39 (OS), Folder 252)
      - 2/28/78. Oakland Training Session. Gary sim HM. 2/22/78. Lois - sim H/M (Box 39 (OS), Folder 253)
      - 2/24/78. Oak Tr. Session. Dan Bakar [Bacar?]. 1/2 tape on "readiness of people" to take on issues. Vivian and Gib [?] (Box 39 (OS), Folder 254)
      - 2/27/78. Oak Tr. - Phoning. "Mert" [?] - Organize [illeg.] H. Mtg. Lois Pryner. (Box 39 (OS), Folder 255)
      - 2/27/78. Oak Tr. Session. CC in Oak 1953. Prep for PV. Persistence. CC - Decoto, Bakersfield, Oxnard, Delano. Ross - persistence. [Illeg.] LA Voter Reg. Sac - Wetback [Ross recording in car 1/23/78 en route to C. [illeg.] from LA] (Box 39 (OS), Folder 256)
      - 4/24/78. Fred W. Ross. History - Negotiation class. La Paz. History SRA - carrots - Mulligan - Hardie - Inspiration (Box 39 (OS), Folder 257)
      - 4/24/78. Fred W. Ross - Hardie training. History - [illeg.] and WRA. [Illeg.] and Evacuation. History end of J.A.'s - Beg. of San Bernardino (Box 39 (OS), Folder 258)
      - 4/24/78. Fred W. Ross. History San Bern. Bell Town, Reds, C.B.-Santa Ana. El M[illeg.] S. L. - Frances and Julie LA (Box 39 (OS), Folder 259)
      - 4/25/78. Fred W. Ross. history. Julie - [illeg.] - Roybal - Alinsky - CPO - CSO. Rios, Nava [?], Lito, Maria, Origin of H.M. History - Birth and development of CSO [illeg.] Voter Reg - Elect of Roybal - Bloody Xmas (Box 39 (OS), Folder 260)
      - 4/25/78. Fred W. Ross. History - Bloody Xmas - Discussion re Roybal v. Ross relations. History - HM with Cesar 6/52. La Paz - CC makes a report. (Box 39 (OS), Folder 261)
      - 4/25/78. La Paz classes. Description of Maravilla to [illeg.]. Hs Mtg with Cesar - my "pitch" (Box 39 (OS), Folder 262)
      - 4/25/78. La Paz classes. From end of HM with Cesar. 4/26/78 La Paz classes. Cesar goes to Decoto [illeg.] (Box 39 (OS), Folder 263)
      - 4/26/78. Fred W. Ross. San Jose. History - San Antonio courts [?] citizenship program - Decoto. Oakland and Salinas. CC in Bakersfield. Ross in San Bern[illeg.] - Brawley. Gary F. (Box 39 (OS), Folder 264)
      - 4/26/78. Fred W. Ross. History - Stockton and Dolores, beginning of Oxnard - Hanford - Brawley. End of Oxnard. CC resigns to start UFW (Box 39 (OS), Folder 265)
      - [April 1978?]. Cesar in Decoto etc. La Paz - Training [?] - [illeg.] students (Box 39 (OS), Folder 266)
    - Audiocassettes, 1978-1984
      - 4/26 [1978?]. La Paz class. Cesar goes to Oxnard. 4/27 - La Paz class. Cesar's Ordeal in Delano - early org'g- hunger (Box 40 (OS), Folder 267)
      - 4/27 [1978?]. La Paz classes. Cesar - [illeg.] - fears - new approaches in early org'g of NFWA. Busses [sic] loaded with women scabs roar into DiGiorgio (Box 40 (OS), Folder 268)
      - 4/27/78. Fed W. Ross. History - Guadalupe GO - Cesar begins UFW. DiGiorgio election, El Mosquito etc. (Box 40 (OS), Folder 269)
      - 4/27/78. La Paz classes. DiGiorgio election - Guimarra strike. Amelia Huerta [?] at DiGiorgio to Salina strike. (Box 40 (OS), Folder 270)
      - 4/27/78. Fred W. Ross. History - 1973 - 600 Wkrs go east to picket. 4/28/78 (Box 40 (OS), Folder 271)
      - 4/28/78. Fred W. Ross. Alinsky before Senat [sic] Fact Finding Com Ovelia [?] Diaz # 30 - CC is on this tape (Box 40 (OS), Folder 272)
      - 4/28/78. La Paz classes. End of Salinas strike - "action and reaction" [illeg.] L.A.-C.S.O. (Box 40 (OS), Folder 273)
      - 4/24/78. La Paz Session with class on Negotiation. I meet Nacho Lopez to Casa Blanca. 10% [illeg.] Lulac - El Mo[illeg.]. San Diego V. Reg. Drive (Box 40 (OS), Folder 274)
      - [April 1978?]. To [illeg.] Mig. Lab. Camp (in car on way to La Paz. Beginning to marriage to grower [?]. In car on way to La Paz Tr. session with Neg's class (Box 40 (OS), Folder 275)
      - 11/22/78. NIA Sessions. Domestic Wkr (Box 40 (OS), Folder 276)
      - 11/24/78. The rap for phone call (Box 40 (OS), Folder 277)
      - [November 1978?]. The PV (Box 40 (OS), Folder 278)
      - [November 1978?]. PV (Box 40 (OS), Folder 279)
      - 1/19/79, Calexico. Fred Ross. 11/20/79 [illeg.], Dirty Tricks, Bloody Summer. [On cassette liner: 11/18/79: History.] (Box 40 (OS), Folder 280)
      - 1/18/79 Calexico. Fred Ross. History of the Farm Workers Movement (Box 40 (OS), Folder 281)
      - 1/19/79. Fred Ross (Box 40 (OS), Folder 282)
      - 1/19/79, Calexico. Fred Ross. History of the Farm Workers Movement (Box 40 (OS), Folder 283)
      - 1/27 [1979], Berkeley. Coords' Mtg. 1/28/79, San Jose staff Mtg. (Box 40 (OS), Folder 284)
      - 9/25/79. Paul and Mike. Salary [?] with Alinsky. Structure- Crazies [?] - Advisory [?] officers, issue [illeg.] Bell Town. Single issue org. (Box 40 (OS), Folder 285)
      - 9/24[29?]/79. Paul and Mike. Very good. (Box 40 (OS), Folder 286)
      - 1/17/80. Fred and Paul. How I org'd CSO - Membs must pay for org. Role of Org in CSO (Box 40 (OS), Folder 287)
      - 1/24/80. Fred and Paul. CSO org'g mtg. (Box 40 (OS), Folder 288)
      - 1/31/80. Fred Ross and Paul (Box 40 (OS), Folder 289)
      - 1/31/80. Fred and Paul. Voting Power - San Diego (Box 40 (OS), Folder 290)
      - 2/7/80 Paul and Fred. Hs Mtgs (Box 40 (OS), Folder 291)
      - 2/7/80. Paul and Fred. Paul and Voting Power Drive (Box 40 (OS), Folder 292)
      - 4/16/80. Fred Ross on Hs Mtgs, organizing (Box 40 (OS), Folder 293)
      - 4/16/80, 4/17/80. Fred Ross on organizing (Box 40 (OS), Folder 294)
      - May 22-23, 1980. Training. Post Morteming in prep for HM (Box 40 (OS), Folder 295)
      - 5/23/80. Oak Training (Box 40 (OS), Folder 296)
      - June, July, Aug. 1980. Oakland Training (Box 40 (OS), Folder 297)
      - June-July 1980. Oakland Boycott training session - Kevin (Box 40 (OS), Folder 298)
      - [summer?] 1980. Oakland. JB - P.V. (Box 40 (OS), Folder 299)
      - 7/80. Oxnard. Training - Artie [?] Reed [?] and Paul David (Box 40 (OS), Folder 300)
      - 8/1/80. HM with Limoniera [?] Wkrs in vidal's back yard (Box 40 (OS), Folder 301)
      - 8/1/80. H Metting with Limoniera [?] Wkrs in Vidal back yard (Box 40 (OS), Folder 302)